RISM Collections at New York University Conferences Guide to the Records of New Perspectives on Caribbean Studies: Toward the 21st Century and Prospects for Caribbean Basin Integration (Conference held at Hunter College, CUNY, August 28-September 1, 1984) RISM.RG.16.(j)
New York University Archives
- Series VIII. Photographs, August 28 - September 1, 1984 (at the Reed Foundation), 141528
  - Subseries b. Digitized Copies of Prints, 141529
    - Session XII. Closing Session and Awards Ceremony, 170428
      - l. to r.: Michael Manley, Vera D. Rubin, Jorge Sol, Sep 1, 1984; 141714 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-109)
      - l. to r.: Michael Manley, Vera D. Rubin, Jorge Sol, Sep 1, 1984; 141713 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-110)
      - l. to r.: Michael Manley, Vera D. Rubin, Jorge Sol, Sep 1, 1984; 141712 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-111)
      - l. to r.: Michael Manley, Vera D. Rubin, Jorge Sol, Sep 1, 1984; 141711 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-112)
      - Elizabeth M. Thomas-Hope, Sep 1, 1984; 141710 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-113)
      - Jorge Sol, Sep 1, 1984; 141709 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-114)
      - Jorge Sol, Michael Manley, Sep 1, 1984; 141708 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-115)
      - Jorge Sol, Michael Manley, Sep 1, 1984; 141707 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-116)
      - l. to r.: Demetrio Boersner, Lloyd Barnet, Jorge Heine, Sep 1, 1984; 141706 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-117)
      - Archie Singham and daughter, Sep 1, 1984; 141705 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-118)
      - l to r: Michael Manley, Peter Weiss, Sep 1, 1984; 141704 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-119)
      - George L. Beckford, Sep 1, 1984; 141703 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-120)
      - Unidentified individuals, Sep 1, 1984; 141702 (Notebook 14, Folder CC84-121)
      - l. to r.: Cora Weiss, Joseph Murphy, Archie Singham, Sep 1, 1984; 141701 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-122)
      - Beasley Haycock, unidentified individual, Denis Benn, Sep 1, 1984; 141700 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-123)
      - Beasley Haycock, unidentified individual, Denis Benn, Sep 1, 1984; 141699 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-124)
      - Beasley Haycock, unidentified individuals, Denis Benn, Sep 1, 1984; 141698 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-125)
      - Erroll Hill, Peter Harvey, unidentified individuals, Lloyd Braithwaite, Sep 1, 1984; 141697 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-126)
      - Unidentified individuals, Don Mills, Sep 1, 1984; 141696 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-127)
      - Wilfred Cartey, unidentified individual, Sep 1, 1984; 141695 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-128)
      - l. to r.: Peter D. Phillips, George L. Beckford, Trevor M. A. Farrell, Helen McEachrane, Sybil Lewis, Sep 1, 1984; 141694 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-129)
      - George Lamming, Sep 1, 1984; 141693 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-130)
      - George Lamming, Michael Manley, Sep 1, 1984; 141692 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-131)
      - l. to r.: Helen McEachrane, Denis Benn, Beasley Haycock, Robert A. Manners, Wilfred Cartey, Aisha Khan, Sep 1, 1984; 141691 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-132)
      - l. to r.: Helen McEachrane, Denis Benn, Beasley Haycock, Robert A. Manners, Wilfred Cartey, Aisha Khan, Sep 1, 1984; 141690 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-133)
      - l. to r.: Helen McEachrane, Denis Benn, Beasley Haycock, Robert A. Manners, Wilfred Cartey, Aisha Khan, Sep 1, 1984; 141689 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-134)
      - Helen McEachrane, unidentified individual, Sep 1, 1984; 141688 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-135)
      - Helen McEachrane, unidentified individual, Sep 1, 1984; 141687 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-136)
      - foreground: Mighty Sparrow; background: Robin Elliot, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individuals, Sep 1, 1984; 141686 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-137)
      - foreground: Mighty Sparrow; background: Robin Elliot, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individuals, Sep 1, 1984; 141685 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-138)
      - foreground: Mighty Sparrow; background: Robin Elliot, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individuals, Sep 1, 1984; 141684 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-139)
      - foreground: Mighty Sparrow; background: Robin Elliot, Vera D. Rubin, unidentified individuals, Sep 1, 1984; 141683 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-140)
      - Robin Elliot, Vera D. Rubin, Mighty Sparrow, unidentified individuals, Archie Singham, Sep 1, 1984; 141682 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-141)
      - June Anderson, Leslie Lett, Sep 1, 1984; 141681 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-142)
      - June Anderson, Leslie Lett, Sep 1, 1984; 141680 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-143)
      - Livia Moller, June Anderson, Sep 1, 1984; 141679 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-144)
      - Jane Gregory Rubin, Reed Rubin, Vera D. Rubin, Sep 1, 1984; 141678 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-145)
      - Mighty Sparrow, Joan Sanders, unidentified individual, George Lamming, Sep 1, 1984; 141677 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-146)
      - l. to r.: Norman P. Girvan, Maurice A. Odle, Jorge Heine, Lloyd Best, Sep 1, 1984; 141676 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-147)
      - l. to r.: Norman P. Girvan, Maurice A. Odle, Jorge Heine, Lloyd Best, Sep 1, 1984; 141675 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-148)
      - l. to r.: Wilfred Cartey, Irene Comitas, Reed Rubin, Christine Donovan, Sep 1, 1984; 141674 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-149)
      - Serving table, Sep 1, 1984; 141673 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-150)
      - Adolfo Aguilar, Sep 1, 1984; 141672 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-151)
      - Lord Nelson, Sep 1, 1984; 141671 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-152)
      - Lord Nelson, Sep 1, 1984; 141670 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-153)
      - Lord Nelson, different view, Sep 1, 1984; 141669 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-154)
      - Lord Nelson, different view, Sep 1, 1984; 141668 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-155)
      - RISM staff: Sheila Bourne, Judith Selakoff, Leanna Selakoff, Sep 1, 1984; 141667 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-156)
      - l. to r.: Dessima Williams, Peter Weiss, Cora Weiss, Lucille Mair, Sep 1, 1984; 141666 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-157)
      - l. to r.: Dessima Williams, Peter Weiss, Cora Weiss, Lucille Mair, Sep 1, 1984; 141665 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-158)
      - Israel D. Drori, Frank McGlynn, Robert L. Hess, Frances Hess, Sep 1, 1984; 141664 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-159)
      - Israel D. Drori, Frank McGlynn, Robert L. Hess, Frances Hess, Sep 1, 1984; 141663 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-160)
      - Joseph Murphy, Mighty Sparrow, Sep 1, 1984; 141662 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-161)
      - Joseph Murphy, Mighty Sparrow, Sep 1, 1984; 141661 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-162)
      - Howard Dodson, Sybil Lewis, Sep 1, 1984; 141660 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-163)
      - Lucille Mair, Sep 1, 1984; 141659 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-164)
      - Archie Singham, Mighty Sparrow, M. G. Smith, Irene Comitas, Lloyd Braithwaite, Ursula Braithwaite, Sep 1, 1984; 141658 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-165)
      - Archie Singham, Mighty Sparrow, M. G. Smith, Irene Comitas, Lloyd Braithwaite, Ursula Braithwaite, Sep 1, 1984; 141657 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-166)
      - M. G. Smith, Sep 1, 1984; 141656 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-167)
      - Merle Hodge, Sep 1, 1984; 141655 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-168)
      - Robert A. Manners, Archie Singham, Helen McEachrane, Alistair Hennesy, Sybil Lewis, Sep 1, 1984; 141654 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-169)
      - Robert A. Manners, Archie Singham, Helen McEachrane, Alistair Hennesy, Sybil Lewis, Sep 1, 1984; 141653 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-170)
      - l. to r.: Peter Weiss, Lloyd Braithwaite, Sep 1, 1984; 141652 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-171)
      - l. to r.: unidentified individual, Lloyd Braithwaite, Sep 1, 1984; 141651 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-172)
      - Rex Nettleford, Sep 1, 1984; 141650 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-173)
      - l. to r.: Adolfo Aguilar, Lambros Comitas, Sep 1, 1984; 141649 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-174)
      - Michael Manley, Peter Weiss, Sep 1, 1984; 141648 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-175)
      - l. to r.: George Lamming, Michael Manley, Sep 1, 1984; 141647 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-176)
      - l. to r.: Jorge Sol, Peter Weiss, Michael Manley, Sep 1, 1984; 141646 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-177)
  - Subseries c. Digitized Copies of Contact Sheets, 170429
    - Roll 43: 37 images, 170430 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-178)
    - Roll 47: 36 images, 170431 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-179)
    - Roll 49: 35 images, 170432 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-180)
  - Subseries d. Printed Photographs, 170433
    - Session XII. Closing Session and Awards Ceremony, 170434
      - l. to r.: Michael Manley, Vera D. Rubin, Jorge Sol, Sept 1, 1984; 170435 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-109)
      - l. to r: Michael Manley, Vera D. Rubin, Jorge Sol, Sept 1, 1984; 170436 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-110)
      - l. to r: Michael Manley, Vera D. Rubin, Jorge Sol, Sept 1, 1984; 170437 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-111)
      - l. to r: Michael Manley, Vera D. Rubin, Jorge Sol, Sept 1, 1984; 170438 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-112)
      - Elizabeth M. Thomas-Hope, Sept 1, 1984; 170439 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-113)
      - Jorge Sol, Sept 1, 1984; 170440 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-114)
      - Jorge Sol, Michael Manley, Sept 1, 1984; 170441 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-115)
      - Jorge Sol, Michael Manley, Sept 1, 1984; 170442 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-116)
      - l. to r: Demetrio Boersner, Lloyd Barnet, Jorge Heine, Sept 1, 1984; 170443 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-117)
      - Archie Singhman and daughter, Sept 1, 1984; 170444 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-118)
      - l. to r: Michael Manley, Peter Weiss, Sept 1, 1984; 170445 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-119)
      - l. to r: George L. Beckford, Sept 1, 1984; 170446 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-120)
      - l. to r: Unidentified individuals, Sept 1, 1984; 170447 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-121)
      - l. to r: Cora Weiss, Joseph Murphy, Archie Singham, Sept 1, 1984; 170448 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-122)
      - Beasley Haycock, unidentified individual, Dennis Benn, Sept 1, 1984; 170449 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-123)
      - Beasley Haycock, unidentified individual, Dennis Benn, Sept 1, 1984; 170450 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-124)
      - Beasley Haycock, unidentified individual, Dennis Benn, Sept 1, 1984; 170451 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-125)
      - l. to r: Erroll Hill, Peter Harvey, unidentified individuals, Lloyd Braithwaite, Sept 1, 1984; 170452 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-126)
      - l. to r: Unidentified individuals, Don Mills, Sept 1, 1984; 170453 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-127)
      - l. to r: Wilfred Cartey, unidentified individual, Sept 1, 1984; 170454 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-128)
      - l. to r: Peter D. Phillips, George L. Backford, Trevor M.A. Farrell, Hillary McEachrane, Sybil Lewis, Sept 1, 1984; 170455 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-129)
      - George Lamming, Sept 1, 1984; 170456 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-130)
      - George Lamming, Michael Manley, Sept 1, 1984; 170457 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-131)
      - l. to r: Helen McEachrane, Dennis Benn, Beasley Haycock, Robert A. Manners, Wilfred Cartey, Aisha Khan, Sept 1, 1984; 170458 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-132)
      - l. to r: Helen McEachrane, Dennis Benn, Beasley Haycock, Robert A. Manners, Wilfred Cartey, Aisha Khan, Sept 1, 1984; 170459 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-133)
      - l. to r: Helen McEachrane, Dennis Benn, Beasley Haycock, Robert A. Manners, Wilfred Cartey, Aisha Khan, Sept 1, 1984; 170460 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-134)
      - Helen McEachrane, unidentified individual, Sept 1, 1984; 170461 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-135)
      - Helen McEachrane, unidentified individual, Sept 1, 1984; 170462 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-136)
      - foreground: Mighty Sparrow; background: Robin Elliot, Vera D. Rubin, unidenitified individuals, Sept 1, 1984; 170463 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-137)
      - foreground: Mighty Sparrow; background: Robin Elliot, Vera D. Rubin, unidenitified individuals, Sept 1, 1984; 170464 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-138)
      - foreground: Mighty Sparrow; background: Robin Elliot, Vera D. Rubin, unidenitified individuals, Sept 1, 1984; 170465 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-139)
      - foreground: Mighty Sparrow; background: Robin Elliot, Vera D. Rubin, unidenitified individuals, Sept 1, 1984; 170466 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-140)
      - Robin Elliot, Vera D. Rubin, Mighty Sparrow, unidentified individuals, Archie Singham, Sept 1, 1984; 170467 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-141)
      - June Anderson, Leslie Lett, Sept 1, 1984; 170470 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-142)
      - June Anderson, Leslie Lett, Sept 1, 1984; 170471 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-143)
      - Livia Moller, June Anderson, Sept 1, 1984; 170472 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-144)
      - Jane Gregory Rubin, Reed Rubin, Vera D. Rubin, Sept 1, 1984; 170473 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-145)
      - Mighty Sparrow, Joan Sanders, unidentified individual, George Lamming, Sept 1, 1984; 170474 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-146)
      - l. to r.: Norman P. Girvan, Maurice A. Odle, Jorge Heine, Lloyd Best, Sept 1, 1984; 170475 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-147)
      - l. to r.: Norman P. Girvan, Maurice A. Odle, Jorge Heine, Lloyd Best, Sept 1, 1984; 170476 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-148)
      - l. to r: Wilfred Cartey, Irene Comitas, Reed Rubin, Christine Donovan, Sept 1, 1984; 170468 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-149)
      - Serving table, Sept 1, 1984; 170477 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-150)
      - Adolfo Aguilar, Sept 1, 1984; 170478 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-151)
      - Lord Nelson, Sept 1, 1984; 170479 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-152)
      - Lord Nelson, Sept 1, 1984; 170480 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-153)
      - Lord Nelson, different view, Sept 1, 1984; 170481 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-154)
      - Lord Nelson, different view, Sept 1, 1984; 170482 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-155)
      - RISM staff: Sheila Bourne, Judith Selakoff, Leanna Selakoff, Sept 1, 1984; 170483 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-156)
      - l. to r.: Dessima Williams, Peter Weiss, Cora Weiss, Lucille Mair, Sept 1, 1984; 170484 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-157)
      - l. to r.: Dessima Williams, Peter Weiss, Cora Weiss, Lucille Mair, Sept 1, 1984; 170485 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-158)
      - l. to r.: Israel D. Drori, Frank McGlynn, Robert L. Hess, Frances Hess, Sept 1, 1984; 170486 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-159)
      - l. to r.: Israel D. Drori, Frank McGlynn, Robert L. Hess, Frances Hess, Sept 1, 1984; 170487 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-160)
      - Joseph Murphy, Mighty Sparrow, Sept 1, 1984; 170488 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-161)
      - Joseph Murphy, Mighty Sparrow, Sept 1, 1984; 170489 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-162)
      - Howard Dodson, Sybil Lewis, Sept 1, 1984; 170490 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-163)
      - Lucille Mair, Sept 1, 1984; 170491 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-164)
      - Archie Singham, Mighty Sparrow, M.G. Smith, Irene Comitas, Lloyd Braithwaite, Ursula Braithwaite, Sept 1, 1984; 170492 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-165)
      - Archie Singham, Mighty Sparrow, M.G. Smith, Irene Comitas, Lloyd Braithwaite, Ursula Braithwaite, Sept 1, 1984; 170493 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-166)
      - M.G. Smith, Sept 1, 1984; 170494 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-167)
      - Merle Hodge, Sept 1, 1984; 170495 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-168)
      - Robert A. Manners, Archie Singham, Helen McEachrane, Alistair Hennesy, Sybil Lewis, Sept 1, 1984; 170496 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-169)
      - Robert A. Manners, Archie Singham, Helen McEachrane, Alistair Hennesy, Sybil Lewis, Sept 1, 1984; 170497 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-170)
      - l. to r.: Peter Weiss, Lloyd Braithwaite, Sept 1, 1984; 170498 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-171)
      - l. to r.: unidentified individual, Lloyd Braithwaite, Sept 1, 1984; 170499 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-172)
      - Rex Nettleford, Sept 1, 1984; 170500 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-173)
      - l. to r.: Adolfo Aguilar, Lambros Comitas, Sept 1, 1984; 170501 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-174)
      - Michael Manley, Peter Weiss, Sept 1, 1984; 170502 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-175)
      - l. to r.: George Lamming, Michael Manley, Sept 1, 1984; 170503 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-176)
      - l. to r.: Jorge Sol, Peter Weiss, Michael Manley, Sept 1, 1984; 170504 (Notebook 14A, Folder CC84-177)
- Series IX. Audio and Video Administrative Files, 141523
  Scope and Contents
  Approximately .25 linear feet (4 folders). Arranged chronologically. This series includes a summary of tape highlights, partial video transcripts, correspondence relating to the recording process and curricula vitae of videographers.
  - Correspondence, curriculum vitae, notes, ephemera, July - Aug 1984; undated; 141527 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Videotape transcription sample, 36 min., undated; 141526 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Timeline for each videotaped session, undated; 141525 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Correspondence, curriculum vitae, proposal, Jan - Mar 1985; undated; 141524 (Box 14, Folder 41)
- Series X. Pre-Publication Papers, July 1984-December 1986, 1984-1986; 170313
  - Lists of conference participants, form letters, ephemera, May- Sept 1984; 170314 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Requests for papers, Sept 1984-Feb 1986; 170315 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Abstracts A-G, 170316 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Abstracts H-Q, [1984]; 170317 (Box 15, File 4)
  - Abstracts S-Z, list of abstracts, [1984]; 170318 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - List of abstracts, Mss. rec'd., Jun 1985; undated; 170319 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Post-conference form letters, Sept-Oct 1984; 170320 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Mailing lists, ephemera, Sept 1984; 170321 (Box 15, File 8)
  - Mailing lists [for labels], undated; 170322 (Box 15, File 9)
  - Form letters by Vera Rubin and Lambors Comitas--conference publication, Dec 1984;June 1985; 170323 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence--publishers, May-Jun 1984; Mar 1985; Oct 1986; 170324 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence--permissions A-C, Oct 1984-Aug 1989; 170325 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence--permissions D-H, Sept 1984-Jan 1985; 170326 (Box 15, File 13)
  - Correspondence--I-R, Oct 1984-July 1985: undated; 170327 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence--permissions S-Z pamphlet, Oct 1984-Dec 1986; undated; 170328 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Series XI. Conference Manuscripts (unpublished) June 1984-January 1985, 170329
  2.0 linear feet (4 boxes). Arranged in order of presentation (see conference programs, Box 16, Folder 1). Although some Mss. titles differ from those listed in the conference programs, this series consists of original conference manuscripts. Highlights include the opening remarks by Vera D. Rubin (see Folder 3), original art work, the closing address by former prime minister Michael Manley and papers associated with the award ceremony. Based on the correspondence and tally sheets in this series, some Mss. were revised or formalized after the conference for publication. Several Mss. were not submitted.
  - Session I, 170505
    - Conference Programs, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170507 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - List of participant manuscripts, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170508 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Session I. Plantation Society and the Contemporary Caribbean, 170330
    - "Opening Remarks," Vera D. Rubin, [Aug-Sept 1984]; 170506 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - "Plantation Economy and Banana Monarchy," Lloyd Best, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170510 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "Caribbean Sugar Plantations: Their Past, and their Probable Future," Manuel Moreno Fraginals, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170511 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - "The Plantation Legacy and the Rise, Decline and Re-Emergence of Transitional Corporations in the Caribbean," Maurice A. Odle, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170512 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - "Overcoming Dependency," Jay R. Mandle, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170513 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - "Reflections on Regional Agricultural Development: Constraints and Potentials," Patrick I. Gomes, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170514 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - "Presence and Decline of the Counter-Plantation System in Dominca," Jean Casimir, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170515 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Discussion Remarks: "Comments on Plantation Society and the Contemporary Caribbean," Norman P. Girvan, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170516 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Session II. Stratification, Pluralism and Sociopolitical Dynamics, 170331
    - "Pluralism in the Non-Hispanic Caribbean," M.G. Smith, [June 1984]; 170517 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - "Pluralism in the Non-Hispanic Caribbean," M.G. Smith (rev.), [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170522 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - "Class, Race and Culture in the Caribbean," Ken Post, [Aug - Sept 1984; 170521 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - "Reforma y Revolutcion en el Caribe," Demetrio Boersner, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170520 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - "Stratification and Social Class in the Hispanic Caribbean (with Special Emphasis on Puerto Rico)," Angel G. Quintero-Rivera, July 1984; 170519 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - "Francaso del Poder Oligarqico en Haiti y Alternativas de Cambio," Suzy Castor, Gerard Pierre-Charles, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170518 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - "Francaso del Poder Oligarqico en Haiti y Alternativas de Cambio," (rev.) Suzy Castor, Gerard Pierre-Charles, Nov 1984; 170523 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - "Voodoo and Politics in Contemporary Haiti," (original and revised copies) Michael S. Laguerre, [Aug - Oct 1984]; 170524 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - "Socialism y Nacionalismo en la Ideologia de La Izquierda del Caribe de Haba Inglesa," Andres Serbin [discussion remarks not included], [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170525 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Session III. Theoretical and Applied Issues in Social Organization, 170332
    - "Anthropology of Caribbean Agrarian Formations," Frank McGlynn, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170529 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - "Power and Privilege in a Small Island Economy: The Case of Trinidad and Tobago," Carl D. Parris, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170528 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - "Social Class and Religious Experience: The Case of Jamaica," Diane J. Austin, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170527 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - "Caribbean Literature and the Schools," Merle Hodge [missing], [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170526 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - "Africans in the Diaspora: Changing Continuities In West Indian and West Africian Sex/Gender Systems," Constance Sutton, [Aug - Oct 1984]; 170530 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Ganja: "A Mono-Crop Alternative," Ansley Hamid [discussion remarks not included], [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170531 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Session IV. Processes of Ethnicity, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170532
    - "Dependenct and Loval Level Conflicts Agrarian Processes in Guyana and Coastal Ecuador," Marilyn Silverman, 170533 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - "Guaymi Labor on a United Brands Subsidiary in Bocas del Toro, Panama and Talamanca, Costa Rica," Philippe Bourgois, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170534 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - "Ethnic Diversity on a Corporate Plantation," (rev.) Philippe Bourgois, Nov 1984; 170535 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - "Ethnicity, Consciousness, and Revolution: The Miskitu/Creole Question in Nicaragua," Galio Gurdian and Edmundo Gordon, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170536 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - "The Tolupan (Jicaque) of Honduras: A Study of Culture Lost," Anne Chapman, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170537 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - "The Decimation of the Indians in Guatemala," Adolfo Aguilar [missing], [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170538 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - "Guyana at the Crossroads of Latin American Politics in the Caribbean." Rita Giacalone de Romero [2], Sept 1984; 170539 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - "Guyana At The Crossroads of Latin American POlitics in the Caribbean." (rev.) Rita Giacalone de Romero [discussion remarks not included], Oct 1984; 170540 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Session V. Nationalism, Independence and Creative Florescence, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170545
    - "Symbolic Expression of Polotics: Cricket and Carnival," Frank E. Manning, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170544 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - "The Impact of National Consciousness on Arts and Literature," John Wickham, [Aug - Sept 1984]; 170543 (Box 17, Folder 16)